【The fate that cannot be liberated】
[해방될 수 없는 운명]
[Episode 9]
[9화]
[To Jiuling]
[지울링에게]
General He.
장군 그.
Lee adult.
이성인.
gentlemen. he.
신사. 그.
I speculate about the marriage between Xingxiang Pavilion and General Mansion
Xingxiang Pavilion과 General Mansion의 결혼에 대해 추측합니다.
Will be arranged soon.
곧 준비될 예정입니다.
When will we receive the wedding invitation?
청첩장은 언제 받을 수 있나요?
My second brother and third brother are not married yet,
둘째오빠와 셋째오빠는 아직 결혼을 안했는데,
So Ling won't get married anytime soon.
그래서 링은 곧 결혼하지 않을 것입니다.
What's more, the young master is seriously ill.
게다가 젊은 주인은 중병에 걸렸습니다.
How could he have a wedding?
그는 어떻게 결혼식을 할 수 있었습니까?
My Lords, please watch your words.
주님, 말씀을 지켜주십시오.
I'm already preparing for the wedding.
나는 벌써 결혼식을 준비하고 있어요.
That's very good. Then we waited for the wedding invitation.
아주 좋습니다. 그런 다음 우리는 청첩장을 기다렸습니다.
I'll take my leave first
나 먼저 이만 떠날게
We will definitely bring generous gifts to the wedding.
우리는 결혼식에 반드시 풍성한 선물을 가져올 것입니다 .
Congratulations.
축하해요.
Yong adult,
용인,
Rong Yu and Ling are definitely going to get married.
Rong Yu와 Ling은 확실히 결혼할 것입니다.
But I have visited your house many times,
하지만 나는 당신 집에 여러 번 방문했는데,
You keep refusing to see me.
당신은 계속 나를 만나기를 거부하고 있습니다.
Why are they bringing up their marriage now?
그들은 왜 지금 결혼 문제를 제기하는 걸까요?
General, you are wrong.
장군님, 당신은 틀렸습니다.
I said there is no need for you to come.
나는 당신이 올 필요가 없다고 말했습니다.
What does this have to do with He Jiuling?
이것이 He Jiuling과 어떤 관련이 있습니까?
She is part of my family now
그녀는 이제 내 가족이에요
No matter if she is dead or alive.
그녀가 죽었든 살았든 상관없습니다.
nonsense! This is complete nonsense.
무의미한 말! 이것은 완전히 말도 안되는 소리입니다.
What does Jiang Rong mean?
장롱이 무슨 뜻인가요?
Does he want me to marry Ling to Rong Yu?
그는 내가 Ling과 Rong Yu와 결혼하기를 원합니까?
Let her die there?
그녀가 거기서 죽게 놔두나요?
Ling is the apple of my eye.
Ling은 내 눈의 사과입니다.
I won't let them torture her.
나는 그들이 그녀를 고문하도록 두지 않을 것입니다.
It doesn't matter what Lord Rong wants.
롱 경이 원하는 것이 무엇인지는 중요하지 않습니다.
What's important? ? ?
무엇이 중요한가요? ? ?
Father, do you still want to keep this promise?
아버지, 아직도 이 약속을 지키고 싶으신가요?
And marry Ling to Rong Yu?
그리고 Ling과 Rong Yu와 결혼할까요?
【He is a mansion】
【그는 저택이다】
Not in a hurry.
서두르지 마세요.
No one showed up the last few nights.
지난 며칠 밤에는 아무도 나타나지 않았습니다.
Everyone is here today.
오늘은 모두가 여기에 있습니다.
I got some good news.
좋은 소식이 있어요.
my left hand
내 왼손
It's now possible to hold things.
이제 물건을 잡는 것이 가능해졌습니다.
Sister-in-law, let me serve you some soup.
형수님, 수프 좀 주세요.
- Be careful. - Actually,
- 조심하세요. - 실제로,
I'm very good at making soup.
나는 수프를 아주 잘 끓인다.
I'll tell you everything next time.
다음에 모든 것을 알려 드리겠습니다.
Why don't you eat?
왜 먹지 않니?
Ling, I'm thinking of a way
링, 나 방법을 생각 중이야
Break off your engagement with Rong Yu.
Rong Yu와의 약혼을 끊으십시오.
Why did you mention this suddenly?
갑자기 이 얘기를 왜 한 겁니까?
This problem will have to be solved sooner or later.
이 문제는 조만간 해결되어야 할 것입니다.
When Rong Yu sent the divorce order,
Rong Yu가 이혼 명령을 보냈을 때
I disagree.
나는 동의하지 않습니다.
It was my fault.
그것은 내 잘못이었습니다.
Rong Yu got the divorce order?
유롱이 이혼명령을 받았나요?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
왜 더 일찍 말하지 않았나요?
At that time I was just
그 당시 나는 단지
Wants you to marry him.
당신이 그와 결혼하기를 원합니다.
How could I possibly tell you?
내가 어떻게 당신에게 말할 수 있겠습니까?
So why now?
그렇다면 왜 지금인가?
You think Rong Yu is a fool.
당신은 Rong Yu가 바보라고 생각합니다.
You despise him. You look down on him.
당신은 그를 경멸합니다. 당신은 그를 무시합니다.
So you want me to break off the engagement.
그래서 당신은 내가 약혼을 파기하길 원해요.
Love that!
정말 좋아요!
You are upright, frank, and sharp-eyed.
당신은 올곧고 솔직하며 눈이 예리합니다.
How could it be so vulgar this time?
이번에는 어떻게 이렇게 저속할 수 있지?
You don't like this marriage either, do you?
당신도 이 결혼을 좋아하지 않죠?
Now father and our big brother are on your side.
이제 아버지와 우리 큰 형이 당신 편이에요.
Why are you not happy?
왜 행복하지 않습니까?
You really want to spend your life with a man
당신은 정말 남자와 인생을 보내고 싶어
Who can't do or understand anything?
아무것도 할 수 없고 이해할 수 없는 사람이 어디 있겠습니까?
Why don't you want to marry a true hero who can ride thousands of miles?
수천 마일을 달릴 수 있는 진정한 영웅과 결혼하고 싶지 않은 이유는 무엇입니까 ?
Across rivers and mountains?
강과 산을 건너?
If I had broken off the engagement when he was still the eldest son of the family,
그 사람이 아직 집안의 장남이었을 때 내가 파혼을 했다면,
I'm very candid.
나는 매우 솔직하다.
But now that he's sick, his future is ruined.
하지만 이제 그가 아프기 때문에 그의 미래는 망가졌습니다.
If I leave now,
지금 떠나면,
I'm afraid
나는 두려워
We will be humiliated by everyone.
우리는 모두에게 굴욕을 당할 것입니다.
Ling, what do you think?
링, 네 생각은 어때?
I
나
Cancel the engagement after he recovers.
그가 회복된 후에 약혼을 취소하십시오.
What if he doesn't recover?
그가 회복되지 않으면 어떻게 되나요?
He will.
그는 할 것이다.
Although Master is unwilling to help,
스승님은 도와줄 생각이 없으시지만,
I am his disciple.
나는 그의 제자입니다.
I'm making a plan. Will you believe me?
나는 계획을 세우고 있어요. 내 말을 믿으시겠습니까?
What if you propose to him soon?
곧 그에게 프로포즈한다면 어떨까요?
Then I will marry him.
그러면 나는 그 사람과 결혼할 것이다.
Are you crazy?
제정신이에요?
I've never been more awake than I am now.
나는 지금보다 더 깨어 있었던 적이 없습니다.
wide awake?
완전히 일어났어?
I think you've lost your mind.
내 생각엔 당신이 정신을 잃은 것 같아요.
you do not know. Jiang Rong? ? ?
넌 몰라. 장롱? ? ?
This is enough.
이것으로 충분합니다.
Ling, sit down.
링, 앉아요.
sit down.
앉아.
I have to tell you.
나는 당신에게 말해야합니다.
I won't discuss this with you.
나는 당신과 이것에 대해 논의하지 않을 것입니다.
I'm just telling you my decision.
나는 단지 내 결정을 당신에게 말할 뿐입니다.
if someone insults us
누군가가 우리를 모욕한다면
Let them do it.
그들이 그렇게 하도록 놔두세요.
But no matter what,
하지만 무슨 일이 있어도,
I will never let you marry Rong Yu.
나는 당신이 용우와 결혼하는 것을 결코 허락하지 않을 것입니다.
You shouldn't go anywhere for a while.
당분간 아무데도 가지 마세요.
Think this through at home.
집에서 이것을 생각해보십시오.
- Ling. - let her go.
- 링. - 그녀를 놓아 줘.
Jiuling.
지울링.
Pay close attention to her these days.
요즘 그녀에게 세심한주의를 기울이십시오.
Don't let her out.
그녀를 내보내지 마세요.
Yes.
예.
Okay, let's eat.
알았어, 먹자.
after dinner,
저녁 식사 후,
I have something else to tell you.
또 말씀드릴 게 있어요.
Jiuling, stop. You're not allowed to go anywhere.
지울링, 그만해. 아무데도 갈 수 없습니다.
Let me go.
가자.
It's been five days.
5일이 지났습니다.
Is something wrong, Miss He?
무슨 문제라도 있나요, Miss He?
However, if something happens to her,
하지만 그녀에게 무슨 일이 생기면
Everyone in the capital will know this.
수도에 있는 모든 사람들이 이 사실을 알게 될 것입니다.
Master, don't wait any longer.
선생님, 더 이상 기다리지 마세요.
She hasn't come yet at this time.
그녀는 지금 아직 오지 않았습니다.
I don't think she will come today.
내 생각엔 그 사람이 오늘은 안 올 것 같아.
Why don't we practice speaking or reading words?
말하기나 단어 읽기 연습을 하면 어떨까요 ?
Or Heshan can perform a sword dance for you.
아니면 허샨(Heshan)이 당신을 위해 검무를 선보일 수도 있습니다.
His sword dance is very good.
그의 검춤이 아주 좋습니다.
Your Majesty.
폐하.
The situation on the southern border has become critical.
남쪽 국경의 상황은 매우 심각해졌습니다.
Your Majesty,
폐하,
I am willing to move my family out of the capital
나는 가족을 수도 밖으로 옮길 의향이 있습니다
And went to Nanjiang to defend.
그리고 방어를 위해 난장(Nanjiang)으로 갔다.
I will take root at the border
나는 국경에 뿌리를 내릴 것이다
Defend Jialin from enemies.
적들로부터 Jialin을 보호하세요.
Jiuling, attached prescription.
Jiuling, 처방전 첨부.
If you have any questions, please feel free to drop me a line.
질문이 있으시면 언제든지 저에게 전화해 주세요.
come over.
이리와.
You two move this over there.
너희 둘이 이걸 저기로 옮겨라.
Yes.
예.
- Put this in there. - Yes.
- 이거 거기에 넣어요. - 예.
Be careful about this. Yes.
이에 주의하세요. 예.
what is going on?
무슨 일이야?
We may have to move.
우리는 이사해야 할 수도 있습니다.
Why are we moving?
우리는 왜 이사하는 걸까요?
My father's position changed.
아버지의 입장이 바뀌었습니다.
We are leaving the capital.
우리는 수도를 떠나고 있습니다.
It seems we are
우리인 것 같아요
Take everything away.
모든 것을 가져가세요.
correct. We are leaving with our father.
옳은. 우리는 아버지와 함께 떠납니다.
And your second brother will never return to the capital.
그리고 당신의 둘째 동생은 결코 수도로 돌아오지 않을 것입니다.
He will meet us there.
그는 그곳에서 우리를 만날 것입니다.
Ling.
링.
Jiuling.
지울링.
Father, why are we leaving the capital?
아버지, 우리는 왜 수도를 떠나는 걸까요?
My oldest brother loved solving crimes at the Department of Justice.
큰 형은 법무부에서 범죄를 해결하는 것을 좋아했습니다.
As soon as my second brother returned to the capital, he was immediately promoted.
둘째 형은 수도로 돌아오자마자 곧바로 승진했다.
He San wanted to enter the palace and serve as King Wu's bodyguard.
허삼은 궁궐에 들어가 무왕의 경호원이 되기를 원했다.
He had been preparing for the spring exam for so long.
그는 오랫동안 봄 시험을 준비해 왔습니다 .
Just because of my marriage,
단지 결혼했다는 이유만으로
Everyone had to give up everything they were doing.
모두가 하던 일을 모두 포기해야 했습니다.
And leave here forever.
그리고 여기서 영원히 떠나세요.
If we want to serve the country
나라에 봉사하고 싶다면
and make friends,
친구도 사귀고,
We can do this anywhere.
우리는 어디서나 이것을 할 수 있습니다.
Well, I'm not going. I'll stay here.
글쎄, 난 안 갈 거야. 나는 여기에 머물 것이다.
I will wait for Rong Yu to recover.
나는 Rong Yu가 회복되기를 기다릴 것입니다.
No one will stay here.
아무도 여기에 머물지 않을 것입니다.
The emperor learned that you are practicing martial arts in school.
황제는 당신이 학교에서 무술을 연습하고 있다는 것을 알게 되었습니다.
So he awarded you the title of General Zuo.
그래서 그는 당신에게 주오 장군이라는 칭호를 수여했습니다.
You have no choice.
너는 선택의 여지가 없어.
Why don't you ask for my opinion?
내 의견을 물어보는 게 어때?
Because I know your opinion.
나는 당신의 의견을 알고 있기 때문입니다.
Do you think you married Rong Yu?
당신은 Rong Yu와 결혼했다고 생각합니까?
Will it change his current situation?
그의 현재 상황이 바뀔까요?
- Father. - Don't you think this is torture for me too?
- 아버지. - 이게 나한테도 고문이라고 생각하지 않아?
If you insist,
당신이 주장하는 경우,
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
I would sacrifice everyone in our family.
나는 우리 가족 모두를 희생할 것이다.
to Rong Yu.
유롱에게.
Chenzhou,
천저우,
tell her
그녀에게
What Rong Yu said.
롱유가 한 말이다.
Rong Yu said that if his father insists on guarding the border,
Rong Yu는 그의 아버지가 국경을 지키겠다고 고집하면
His contributions would make emperors and ministers fear him.
그의 공헌은 황제 와 장관들이 그를 두려워하게 만들었습니다 .
This will not end well for my father.
이것은 아버지에게 좋게 끝나지 않을 것입니다.
N-not
아뇨
It ends well.
잘 끝났습니다.
DD-Mold
DD-금형
In combat?
전투 중인가요?
Died for the family forest,
가족의 숲을 위해 죽었습니다.
for the people,
사람들을 위해,
It is the glory of our family.
우리 가문의 영광입니다.
so,
그래서,
Rong Yu's prophecy
용우의 예언
I'm not scared at all.
나는 전혀 무서워하지 않습니다.
Yihua and I are also willing to die for Jialin.
Yihua와 나도 Jialin을 위해 기꺼이 죽을 각오가 되어 있습니다.
Qingxing and Qiu Ting will not live alone.
Qingxing과 Qiu Ting은 혼자 살지 않습니다.
Ling,
링,
This time it's not all about you.
이번에는 당신에 관한 것이 아닙니다.
The emperor mentioned many times
황제가 여러번 언급한
Borders need to be guarded.
국경은 보호되어야 합니다.
We couldn't say no.
우리는 거절할 수 없었습니다.
Follow me and your brothers into battle,
나와 네 형제를 따라 전투에 참여하라.
In order to protect the people of Jialin,
가림 사람들을 보호하기 위해
It can also ensure Rong Yu’s safety.
또한 Rong Yu의 안전도 보장할 수 있습니다.
for the rest of his life.
남은 생애 동안.
Ling,
링,
I also want to see you get married and have children.
나도 당신이 결혼해서 아이를 갖는 모습을 보고 싶어요 .
I want to see your happy life.
당신의 행복한 삶을 보고 싶습니다.
but if i stay in the capital
하지만 내가 수도에 머무르면
Saw you marrying a fool
네가 바보와 결혼하는 걸 봤어
And was scolded and tortured by others,
그리고 다른 사람들에게 꾸지람과 고문을 당했고,
Why do I have to live such a miserable life?
나는 왜 이렇게 비참한 삶을 살아야 하는가?
And give up my strength of character?
그리고 나의 성격의 힘을 포기합니까?
even better is
심지어 더 좋은 건
I'm going the way we should be going.
나는 우리가 가야 할 길을 가고 있습니다.
Now that we've reached this point,
이제 이 지점에 도달했으니,
stay or leave,
머물거나 떠나거나,
up to you.
당신한테 달렸습니다.
I don't believe there is heaven
나는 천국이 있다고 믿지 않는다
Nor in destiny.
운명에도 없습니다.
I believe that humans have the ability to conquer nature.
저는 인간에게는 자연을 정복할 수 있는 능력이 있다고 믿습니다.
I, He Jiuling,
나, He Jiuling,
I am willing to die for Jialin .
나는 Jialin을 위해 기꺼이 죽겠습니다 .
be prepared.
준비하세요.
We will set off for Nanjiang
난장(南江)으로 출발합니다
the day after tomorrow.
모레.
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
If we knew the outcome from the beginning
처음부터 결과를 알았다면
Shouldn't I give you hope?
희망을 주어야 하지 않겠습니까?
Even though I really want to see you again
꼭 다시 보고 싶어도
before we part,
우리가 헤어지기 전에,
but,
하지만,
I can not.
나는 할 수 없다.
I shouldn't.
나는해서는 안된다.
Please forget about me for a moment.
잠시만 저를 잊어주세요.
There are many rare and exotic grasses in Nanjiang .
난장에는 희귀하고 이국적인 풀이 많이 있습니다 .
I will prepare an antidote
해독제를 준비할게요
as soon as possible.
최대한 빨리.
【Rong's Mansion】
【롱 저택】
The master is here.
주인님이 여기 계십니다.
Master, take a look.
선생님, 좀 보세요.
This is the note you wrote earlier. Take it.
아까 쓰셨던 메모입니다. 가져.
Does he come to study every day?
그 사람은 매일 공부하러 오나요?
Yes, he just doesn’t know him well yet.
네, 그 사람은 아직 그를 잘 모릅니다.
The wind is a bit strong.
바람이 좀 강하네요.
The young master’s fault is bad.
젊은 주인의 잘못은 나쁘다.
And there's no stove here.
그리고 여기에는 난로가 없습니다.
Don't come here again.
다시는 여기에 오지 마세요.
You can get him whatever he wants to read .
그가 읽고 싶어하는 것은 무엇이든 얻을 수 있습니다 .
Yes.
예.
This is the owner's thing.
이건 주인의 일이에요.
- be careful. - Yes Yes.
- 조심하세요. - 예 예.
Be careful.
조심하세요.
Ling, how is the packaging?
링씨, 포장은 어때요?
We'll leave early tomorrow morning.
우리는 내일 아침 일찍 떠날 거예요.
Have you packed everything?
짐은 다 꾸렸나요?
Jiuling, Atan said she will come to see you off tomorrow morning.
Jiuling, Atan은 내일 아침에 당신을 배웅하러 올 것이라고 말했습니다.
I'm going out to say goodbye to a few close friends later.
나중에 친한 친구들 몇 명과 작별 인사를 하러 나갈 예정이에요 .
perhaps,
아마도,
We won't be back.
우리는 돌아오지 않을 것이다.
We will die on the Nanjiang battlefield.
우리는 난장 전장에서 죽을 것이다.
Will never come back.
다시는 돌아오지 않을 것이다.
Never see him again.
다시는 그를 만나지 마세요.
???A bouquet of flowers? ? ?
???꽃다발? ? ?
??? bloom for you? ? ?
???당신을 위해 피어나요? ? ?
??? wonderful love? ? ?
???멋진 사랑? ? ?
??? Make me cry and sad? ? ?
??? 나를 울리고 슬프게 만드나요? ? ?
??? A touch of lovesickness makes me sad? ? ?
??? 약간의 상사병이 나를 슬프게 만든다? ? ?
???I can only promise you the next life? ? ?
???다음 생은 약속드릴 수 밖에 없나요? ? ?
Master.
주인.
??? I am crazy for you. Will I stay and find you? ? ?
??? 난 너한테 미쳤어. 내가 머물면서 당신을 찾을 수 있을까요? ? ?
???Give me love in the next life? ? ?
???다음생에도 사랑을 주세요? ? ?
??? Lend me the wish of this life? ? ?
??? 이번생의 소원을 빌려주실래요? ? ?
??? I want to become a butterfly and be obsessed with flowers like you? ? ?
??? 나도 나비가 되어 너처럼 꽃에 푹 빠져보고 싶다? ? ?
???The land is still the same? ? ?
???땅은 아직도 그대로인가요? ? ?
??? Can withstand spring rain and autumn rain? ? ?
??? 봄비, 가을비를 견딜 수 있을까? ? ?
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
Master, where are you going?
선생님, 어디로 가시나요?
Slow down, Master. slow down.
천천히 하세요, 마스터. 천천히 해.
???A bouquet of flowers? ? ?
???꽃다발? ? ?
??? bloom for you? ? ?
???당신을 위해 피어나요? ? ?
??? wonderful love? ? ?
???멋진 사랑? ? ?
??? Make me cry and sad? ? ?
??? 나를 울리고 슬프게 만드나요? ? ?
??? A touch of lovesickness makes me sad? ? ?
??? 약간의 상사병이 나를 슬프게 만든다? ? ?
???I can only promise you the next life? ? ?
???다음 생은 약속드릴 수 밖에 없나요? ? ?
how dare you! Who dares to break into Rong Mansion?
어떻게 감히! 누가 감히 롱맨션에 침입하겠습니까?
???Give me love in the next life? ? ?
???다음생에도 사랑을 주세요? ? ?
??? Lend me the wish of this life? ? ?
??? 이번생의 소원을 빌려주실래요? ? ?
??? I want to become a butterfly and be obsessed with flowers like you? ? ?
??? 나도 나비가 되어 너처럼 꽃에 푹 빠져보고 싶다? ? ?
???The land is still the same? ? ?
???땅은 아직도 그대로인가요? ? ?
??? Can withstand spring rain and autumn rain? ? ?
??? 봄비, 가을비를 견딜 수 있을까? ? ?
??? I am destined to meet you and wait for your return? ? ?
??? 나는 당신을 만나고 당신의 복귀를 기다릴 운명입니까? ? ?
???Give me love in the next life? ? ?
???다음생에도 사랑을 주세요? ? ?
??? Lend me the wish of this life? ? ?
??? 이번생의 소원을 빌려주실래요? ? ?
??? I want to become a butterfly and be obsessed with flowers like you? ? ?
??? 나도 나비가 되어 너처럼 꽃에 푹 빠져보고 싶다? ? ?
???The land is still the same? ? ?
???땅은 아직도 그대로인가요? ? ?
??? Can withstand spring rain and autumn rain? ? ?
??? 봄비, 가을비를 견딜 수 있을까? ? ?
??? I am destined to meet you and wait for your return? ? ?
??? 나는 당신을 만나고 당신의 복귀를 기다릴 운명입니까? ? ?
Since you are leaving tomorrow, why do you come here?
내일 떠날 예정인데 왜 여기에 오나요?
what are you waiting for?
무엇을 기다리고 있나요?
Pulled the young master back.
젊은 주인을 뒤로 끌어 당겼습니다.
Yes Yes.
예 예.
Be gentle. Don't hurt him.
부드럽게 행동하세요. 그를 다치게 하지 마세요.
Master, Master, please come down.
스승님, 스승님, 내려오세요.
Be careful, Master.
조심하세요, 마스터.
Master.
주인.
Master, Master.
스승님, 스승님.
Be careful, Master. Be careful.
조심하세요, 마스터. 조심하세요.
Be careful, Master.
조심하세요, 마스터.
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
come over.
이리와.
How lucky I am in this life.
나는 이생에서 얼마나 운이 좋은지.
Starting tonight,
오늘 밤부터,
I may never see you again.
나는 당신을 다시는 볼 수 없을지도 모릅니다.
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
even if i am
내가 그렇다 해도
far away from you
너에게서 멀리 떨어져
I will pray for you.
나는 너를 위해기도 할거야.
I am leaving.
저 이제가요.
Don't miss me.
나를 놓치지 마세요.
I have no future.
나에게는 미래가 없습니다.
forget me.
날 잊어 줘.
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
[Jialin]
[가림]
What Lord?
몇 주.
I wish you a safe journey.
안전한 여행을 기원합니다.
careful.
주의 깊은.
Miss He.
미스 헤.
painting.
그림.
This is Master Rong’s portrait for you.
이것은 당신을 위한 Master Rong의 초상화입니다.
Don't be so gloomy.
너무 우울해하지 마세요.
Go and stop the young master.
가서 젊은 주인을 막아라.
Master, Master, Master, Master.
마스터, 마스터, 마스터, 마스터.
——He Jiuling. - You can't go out.
——그 Jiuling. - 나갈 수 없어요.
I want to find He Jiuling.
He Jiuling을 찾고 싶습니다.
【Rongfu】 You can't go out.
[롱푸] 나갈 수 없습니다.
Master.
주인.
[Nanjiang]
[난장]
The second sister-in-law's throwing skills have improved again.
둘째 처제의 씨름 실력이 또 좋아졌습니다.
This time, even I couldn't see the flaw.
이번에는 나조차도 결점을 볼 수 없었다.
You're asking for a beating.
당신은 구타를 요구하고 있습니다.
Stop fooling around.
장난은 그만둬.
Jiuling's swordsmanship is getting better and better.
Jiuling의 검술이 점점 좋아지고 있습니다.
After dinner, I want to have a fight with you.
저녁 식사 후에는 당신과 싸우고 싶습니다.
Give me a break.
나에게 휴식을 주세요.
You are the weakest one in the family.
당신은 가족 중 가장 약한 사람입니다.
If you were my sparring partner, I would feel like this is a waste of my time.
당신이 내 스파링 파트너라면 시간 낭비라고 느낄 것입니다.
He Jiuling, don't be so proud.
He Jiuling, 너무 자랑스러워하지 마세요.
One day, I will definitely be able to defeat you.
언젠가는 반드시 당신을 이길 수 있을 겁니다.
Jiuling, lie down.
지울링, 누워라.
look. I knocked down the best
바라보다. 나는 최고를 쓰러뜨렸다
In our home.
우리 집에서.
He Qiuting, you are really looking for death.
그는 Qiuting, 당신은 정말로 죽음을 찾고 있습니다.
It's time to go home and have dinner.
집에 가서 저녁을 먹을 시간이에요.
let's go.
갑시다.
I really hate these twins.
나는 이 쌍둥이를 정말 싫어한다.
Do you want to quarrel or eat?
싸우고 싶나요, 아니면 먹고 싶나요?
eat you. May I?
너를 먹어라. 나는 할 수있다?
What did you say? I didn't hear it.
뭐라고 하셨나요? 나는 그것을 듣지 못했습니다.
running. running. running.
달리기. 달리기. 달리기.
The second sister-in-law is going to beat us.
두 번째 시누이가 우리를 이길 것입니다.
Let's eat.
먹자.
I love you.
사랑해요.
Be good.
잘 지내세요.
The second sister-in- law drinks a lot.
둘째 형수는 술을 많이 마십니다.
Drink more.
더 많이 마셔보세요.
Why do you say these things to him every day?
왜 맨날 그 사람한테 그런 말을 해?
you must. He can understand.
당신은해야합니다. 그는 이해할 수 있습니다.
You just need to say it once a day.
하루에 한 번씩만 말하면 됩니다.
Mom loves you.
엄마는 당신을 사랑해요.
Then he will be beautiful
그러면 그 사람은 아름다울 거야
It’s a pleasure to be your child.
당신의 자녀가 되어 기쁘네요.
Brother, you have to say this too.
형님, 이것도 말해야 해요.
Say it. Say it now. I want to hear it.
말해. 지금 말해보세요. 나는 그것을 듣고 싶다.
What should I say?
무슨 말을 해야 할까요?
Say, daddy loves you.
아빠가 당신을 사랑한다고 말해 보세요.
No, I can not.
아니 난 할 수 없어.
Come on, brother. Say it.
어서, 형제. 말해.
Say it.
말해.
explain? ? ? All right. I'll say it.
설명하다? ? ? 괜찮은. 나는 그것을 말할 것이다.
I? ? ?
나? ? ?
- eat. eat. - Eat.
- 먹다. 먹다. - 먹다.
Stop embarrassing him.
그를 당황하게 하지 마세요.
Please have a meal
식사해주세요
Now, our sister-in-law is the most important thing.
이제 우리 형수님이 가장 중요합니다.
here,
여기,
There is a chicken drumstick.
닭다리가 있습니다.
no no.
아니 아니.
They cook just for me every day.
그들은 매일 나만을 위해 요리를 해줘요.
I can't eat that much.
나는 그렇게 많이 먹을 수 없습니다.
Just eat this?
이것만 먹어?
This is for you, Ling.
이건 당신을 위한 거예요, 링.
Thanks.
감사해요.
This is for you, Father.
이것은 아버지를 위한 것입니다.
OK
좋아요
You've just recovered from a cold.
당신은 방금 감기에서 회복되었습니다.
You still have to take care of yourself.
당신은 여전히 ​​​​자신을 돌봐야합니다.
All right.
괜찮은.
Ling, give you another one.
링, 하나 더 주세요.
I'm done.
난 끝났어.
Thank you, Jiuling. I love you.
고마워요, 지울링님. 사랑해요.
Nowadays, it is really rare for the whole family to be together.
요즘은 온 가족이 함께 모이는 일이 정말 드물어요.
Let's drink together.
같이 마시자.
cheers.
건배.
In this year’s martial arts competition in Nanjiang,
올해 난장(南江) 무술대회에서는
First prize is a co-leadership position.
1등상은 공동 리더 자리입니다.
There are also rewards for other levels,
다른 레벨에 대한 보상도 있습니다.
It's just some medicinal materials like nine-segmented beetles.
그것은 단지 아홉마디 딱정벌레와 같은 약용 물질일 뿐입니다.
It is nothing special.
특별한 것은 아닙니다.
Qiuting,
치우팅,
Don't just eat.
그냥 먹지 마세요.
Do you want to register?
등록하시겠습니까?
Although I am good at martial arts,
무술을 잘하지만
There is always someone else better.
항상 더 나은 사람이 있습니다.
I don’t think I’ll sign up.
나는 가입하지 않을 것 같아요.
If you think so, you can still get better.
그렇게 생각한다면 여전히 나아질 수 있습니다.
Chenzhou, register him.
천저우, 그를 등록하세요.
- Father. I? ? ? - Horseback archery, sticks, spears, knives,
- 아버지. 나? ? ? - 말을 타고 활쏘기, 막대기, 창, 칼,
Sword, array, hook, halberd, dart? Which one do you choose?
검, 배열, 갈고리, 미늘창, 다트? 당신은 어느 것을 선택합니까?
which one?
어느 것?
for me,
나를 위한,
There is no difference. I? ? ?
다른 점이 없다. 나? ? ?
OK Since there is no difference,
좋아요 별차이가 없으니까,
I would just register everything for him.
나는 그를 위해 모든 것을 등록하겠습니다.
What? What?
무엇? 무엇?
Did you two lie to me on purpose?
너희 둘이 나한테 고의로 거짓말을 한 거야?
Jiuling won first place last year.
Jiuling은 작년에 1위를 차지했습니다.
Won't she be allowed to participate this year?
올해는 참가할 수 없나요?
Why are you messing with me?
왜 나한테 장난치는 거야?
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
???해질녘 노을 아래서요? ? ?
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
???나는 먼 곳으로 수천 마일을 여행했다고요? ? ?
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
???달빛아래 피아노 연주? ? ?
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
???이 음료수는 잊혀지지 않을까요? ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
???우리의 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔으로 가득 차 있습니까? ? ?
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 밝은 은하계로 결정화되기를 원하시나요 ???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 조용히 돌아서서 결혼증명서를 닫았나요? ? ?
???Ask how many stars are there in the sky? ? ?
???하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요. ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
???우리의 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔으로 가득 차 있습니까? ? ?
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 밝은 은하계로 결정화되기를 원하시나요 ???
???I gently caress the guzheng, waiting for passers-by like you???
???나는 고젱을 부드럽게 어루만지며 당신같은 행인을 기다린다???
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
???그럼 당신은 나의 불용성 유대인가요? ? ?